Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Deans Papers, 1929-1999, undated, 95 Linear Feet (63.5 boxes)
  - Dean Paul Carrington, 1968-1989, bulk 1978-1988, undated.
    - Office of Major Projects, Council Meeting, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Office of Major Projects, 1986-1987 (8 folders) (Box 51)
    - Duke Law Magazine, 1982-1986 (Box 51)
    - Estate Planning Conference, 1980 (Box 51)
    - Duke Property Development Council, 1985-1987 (Box 51)
    - Continuing Legal Education, 1980-1987 (Box 51)
    - Council of Professional Education, 1985-1987 (Box 51)
    - Law School Building, 1962, 1981, undated (Box 51)
    - Renovation, 1979-1980 (Box 51)
    - Building Planning, Architects, 1984-1988 (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Law School Feasibility Study, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Building Plans, 1976-1979 (Box 51)
    - Space Allocation Memo, 1980 (Box 51)
    - Building Renovations, Tom Croft, 1983 (Box 51)
    - Building Improvements, Tom Croft, 1983, undated (Box 51)
    - Law School Annex, 1984 (Box 51)
    - Renovation Application Process, 1981 (Box 51)
    - Alumni Admissions Interviews, 1984, undated (Box 52)
    - Alumni Admissions Interviewers, 1985-1986 (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - Secretarial Services, 1980-1984 (Box 52)
    - Self Study, 1985 (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Spouse Assistance Program, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Student Files Memo, 1980 (Box 52)
    - Self-Study Report, 1986 (Box 52)
    - Student Funded Fellowship Program, 1979-1986 (Box 52)
    - Subvention, 1980 (Box 52)
    - Tuition, 1981-1986 (Box 52)
    - Tuition Count, Manager, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
    - Placement, 1978-1988 (4 folders) (Box 52)
    - Duke Law School Rules, 1973, 1978-1985, undated (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - New Admission Rules, 1981 (Box 52)
    - New Rules on Student Files, 1981 (Box 52)
    - Student Rules, 1981, undated (Box 52)
    - Academic and Disciplinary Standards, Student Rules, 1980-1981 (Box 52)
    - Performing Arts Council, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Student Travel and Tuition, 1980, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, Personnel, 1986 (Box 52)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, Exactions, 1984-1985 (Box 52)
    - Clerkships, 1988 (Box 52)
    - Office Assignments, 1985-1987 (Box 52)
    - Machemer, Deborah, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Appointments, 1986-1987 (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - North Carolina Legal Services, 1984-1985 (Box 52)
    - Weistart Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
    - Legal Research Program, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
    - Joint Study, Law and Economics, Law and Philosophy, Crauford Goodwin, 1982-1988 (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Business School, Dean Keller, 1970, 1981-1987 (Box 53)
    - Joint Degree, 1981-1986 (Box 53)
    - Law Journal, 1976-1988 (Box 53)
    - Law and Economics, Law and History, 1984-1985 (Box 53)
    - Support Services, 1978-1986 (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Chinese Students, 1985-1987 (Box 53)
    - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, 1985-1987 (Box 53)
    - China Law Reports, 1984 (Box 53)
    - Hangzhou University, 1984-1987 (Box 53)
    - Nanjing University, 1987, undated (Box 53)
    - Southwest Institute of Politics and Law, People's Republic of China, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
    - China Exchange, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Chinese Student Resumes, 1986, undated (Box 53)
    - Committee on Legal Education Exchange with China, 1985-1988 (4 folders) (Box 53)
    - China, Jilin University, 1985-1986 (Box 53)
    - China, C and C Law Offices, 1985-1987 (Box 53)
    - China Law Firms, 1985, undated (Box 53)
    - People's University, 1984-1988 (Box 53)
    - University of International Business and Economics, 1984-1988 (Box 53)
    - Students Interested in China, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Duke Students in China, 1985-1987 (Box 53)
    - China, Miscellaneous, 1983-1988 (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - The Duke Center for Studies of Law on Investment and Trade in China, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Chinese Student Resumes, 1987-1988 (Box 53)
    - Chinese Travel, 1983-1984 (Box 53)
    - Fudan University, 1984-1985 (Box 53)
    - Beijing University, 1984-1987 (Box 54)
    - China Law Program Report, 1985-1987 (Box 54)
    - China Grants, 1987-1988 (Box 54)
    - China History, Budget, Income Statements, 1987 (Box 54)
    - Chinese Legal Program, 1985 (Box 54)
    - China Law Association (C.L.A.), Correspondence with Law Firms, 1985-1988 (3 folders) (Box 54)
    - China, Dechert, Price and Rhoads Fellowship, 1985-1987 (Box 54)
    - Ministry of Education, 1984-1988 (Box 54)
    - China Law Association, 1982-1985 (Box 54)
    - Appointments Committee, 1985-1986 (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1981-1988 (3 folders) (Box 54)
    - Faculty Calendar, 1985-1987 (Box 54)
    - Financial Aid, 1985-1987 (Box 54)
    - Federal Aid to Higher Education, 1982, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Financial Aid Planning, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Duke Legal Education Loan Fund, 1982, 1987, undated (Box 54)
    - Work Study, undated (Box 54)
    - Equal Access, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Duke in Denmark, 1984-1988 (3 folders) (Box 54)
    - Travel to San Francisco and Denmark, 1987 (Box 54)
    - Currie Lecture, 1978-1987, 1989 (Box 54)
    - Duke Bar Association Activities and Memorandums, 1984-1987 (Box 54)
    - Mosteller, Robert, 1984-1985, undated (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Van Alstyne, William, 1972-1983 (4 folders) (Box 55)
    - Schroeder, Chris, 1982-1983 (Box 55)
    - Pratt, Walter F., 1984, undated (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1982-1985 (5 folders) (Box 55)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Subcommittee on Clerkship Selection Guidelines, 1985-1986 (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Moot Court Board, 1979-1990 (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Major Projects, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56)
    - Asian/Pacific Studies Institute, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1979-1986 (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Van Alstyne, william, Interpretations of the First Amendment, undated (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Association of American Law Schools, General Correspondence and Miscellaneous Publications, 1979-1987 (Box 56)
    - Association of American Law Schools Memoranda, 1979-1984 (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - American Bar Association, 1979-1988 (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Human Resources, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Comparative and International Legal Studies, 1985-1987 (Box 56)
    - International Graduate Students, 1985, undated (Box 56)
    - International Studies Japan, 1984-1988 (Box 56)
    - Legal Studies, Korea, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Proposed Program in Canadian Legal Studies, 1981, undated (Box 56)
    - Program in Asian Legal Studies, 1981-1987 (Box 56)
    - International Studies, Asia, undated (Box 56)
    - Islamic and Arabian Development Studies, 1983 (Box 56)
    - International Studies, Canada, 1984 (Box 56)
    - International and Comparitive Law Institute, 1982-1983, undated (Box 56)
    - Duke International Law Society, 1985-1987 (Box 56)
    - Atlantic Coast Conference Golf Tournament, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Council on Legal Education Opportunity, 1974-1987 (Box 56)
    - Bulletin, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
    - Asbestos, 1979-1988 (Box 56)
    - Building Security, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
    - Clinical Studies, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Clinical Studies Grant Application, 1984 (Box 57)
    - Research Committee, Research and Faculty Development, 1978-1986 (Box 57)
    - Sunset Committee (Weistart), 1985 (Box 57)
    - Saturday Seminar Committee, 1984 (Box 57)
    - Trustee Committee for Institutional Advancement, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Planning Committee, 1979-1987 (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - International Legal Studies, 1981-1987 (Box 57)
    - Financial Aid Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
    - Special Committee on Joint Degree Programs, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Judical Clerkship committee, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
    - Joint Studies Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 57)
    - Library Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 57)
    - Placement Committee, 1981 (Box 57)
    - Compensation Review, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Graduate and Independent Study Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 57)
    - International and Comparative Studies Committee, 1982-1988 (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - North Carolina Bar, continuing Legal Education Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 57)
    - Bench, Bar, and Law Liason Committee, 1978-1988 (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - North Carolina State Bar, 1984-1988 (Box 57)
    - Alumni, 1987 (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - Competence of New Admitees, 1985 (Box 57)
    - North Carolina Bar, General Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 57)
    - Internship and Clerkship Sub-Committee, 1985 (Box 57)
    - American Bar Association, Deans and Faculty Salaries, 1981 (Box 57)
    - Law Dedicated Television Network, 1984 (Box 57)
    - National Council for Annual Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
    - Major Projects Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
    - National Council for the Law School Fund, 1985-1987 (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - Correspondence with Other Deans, Regarding Chairs, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Major Projects, Kenan Family, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Major Projects, Tunnell, 1987-1988 (Box 58)
    - Sparks Fund, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Duke Law School Reunion, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Office of Major Projects, 1988 (9 folders) (Box 58)
    - Major Projects Council Meeting, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Major Projects Correspondence and Memorandums, 1987-1988 (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - Building Alterations, 1978-1980, undated (Box 58)
    - Renovation, 1978 (Box 58)
    - Building Advisory committee, 1984-1985 (Box 59)
    - Building Planning Capital Funds, 1983-1988 (Box 59)
    - Building, Ross, Johnston and Kersting, 1981-1986 (Box 59)
    - Building Renovation, 1983 (Box 59)
    - New Building, 1985 (Box 59)
    - Building Planning, 1984-1986 (Box 59)
    - Building, Law School Development Committee, 1985 (Box 59)
    - Ross Letter, 1985 (Box 59)
    - Howell Heflin Honorary Degree, 1986-1988, undated (Box 59)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Alumni Office, 1987-1988 (Box 59)
    - Alumni, 1985-1986 (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Corporate Counsel List, 1987 (Box 59)
    - Alumni Council, 1980-1986 (Box 59)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid Form Letters, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Alumni Judges, 1986-1987 (Box 59)
    - Alumni, Academic, undated (Box 59)
    - Alumni, Corporations, 1986 (Box 59)
    - Alumni, Public Sector, 1983 (Box 59)
    - Alumni, Capital Gifts, 1984 (Box 59)
    - Alumni Travel, 1985 (Box 59)
    - Autonomy, 1984-1985 (Box 59)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1981-1985 (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Annual Dean Reports to Alumni, 1981-1986 (Box 59)
    - Dean's Letter to Alumni, 1980-1986 (Box 59)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1985-1986 (Box 59)
    - Clerkship Guidelines, 1986 (Box 59)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1985-1987 (folder 1 of 3) (Box 59)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1985-1987 (folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 60)
    - Health, Education and Welfare Inquiry, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Rockefeller Grant Preparation, 1981 (Box 60)
    - Grants, Special Projects, 1974-1982, undated (Box 60)
    - Havighurst Grant, 1979-1982 (Box 60)
    - Grant Forms, 1980, undated (Box 60)
    - Havighurst, Clark G., 1979-1986 (Box 60)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference Program committee, 1982-1985 (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Black American Law Students Association, 1979-1983 (Box 60)
    - Administrative Organization of the Law School, 1981-1985 (Box 60)
    - Duke University, Equal Opportunity, 1979-1985, undated (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Sugar Industry Case Agreements and Drafts, 1986-1988 (3 folders) (Box 60)
    - Sugar Industry Case, Evidence, 1986 (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Philippines Sugar Case, 1986-1987 (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Philipines Sugar Addresses, 1986 (Box 61)
    - Philippines Sugar Trip, 1986 (Box 61)
    - Philippines Sugar Correspondence, 1986 (Box 61)
    - Duke Public Interest Law Consoritum, 1986 (Box 61)
    - Philippines Sugar Telexes, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
    - Philippines Sugar, Memos from Faculty, 1986 (Box 61)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Executive Committee, 1984-1987 (7 folders) (Box 61)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Federal Aid, 1984 (Box 61)
    - The Barton-Gillet Company, 1986 (Box 61)
    - CAP Gift and Building Fund Prospects, 1986, undated (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - CAP Gifts Director, 1986-1987 (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - Case Committee (North Carolina Bar), 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Dean Pamela B. Gann, 1988-1999, undated.
    Pamela B. Gann was dean of the law school from 1988 to 1999. This material is restricted for 25 years from date of origin. Contact research services for more information.
    - Recommendations, A-C, 1989-1994 (Box 62)
    - Recommendations, D-G, 1989-1995 (Box 62)
    - Recommendations, H-L, 1989-1995 (Box 62)
    - Recommendations, M-P, 1988-1995 (Box 62)
    - Recommendations, R-S, 1989-1995 (Box 62)
    - Recommendations, T-Z, 1989-1993 (Box 62)
    - Personal Letters, 1987-1999 (3 folders) (Box 62)
    - Reprint Permissions, 1986-1989 (Box 62)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1988-1994 (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - Provost Common Fund, 1993-1996 (Box 62)
    - Kenan Institute and Rollie Tillman, 1989-1990 (Box 62)
    - PACOR Subcommittee, 1991-1994, undated (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - Planning Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 63)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1993-1995 (Box 63)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1999 (Box 63)
    - International Law Candidates, 1998 (Box 63)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1996-1998 (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Faculty Appointments Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 63)
    - Eponymous Chairs, 1997-1998 (Box 63)
    - Shimm Chair Nomination, 1989 (Box 63)
    - Dellinger Chair Nomination, 1991 (Box 63)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1993-1996 (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Chaired Professorships, 1993-1998 (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Provost Correspondence, 1995-1999 (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Ad Hoc Retirement Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 63)
    - Provost Correspondence, 1988-1995 (folder 1 of 3) (Box 63)
    - Provost Correspondence, 1988-1995 (folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 64)
    - Chaired Professorships, 1989-1992 (Box 64)
    - Provost Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
    - Ukranian Legal Foundation, 1993 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, University of North Carolina Law School, 1991-1994 (Box 64)
    - Politically Correct Speech, 1991-1995 (Box 64)
    - Research Support, 1993 (Box 64)
    - Research Support, 1989-1993 (Box 64)
    - Research (Brad Blower), 1986-1987 (Box 64)
  - Associate Dean John D. Johnston Jr., 1959-1968, undated.
    John Johnston was an associate dean of the law school; the exact dates of his tenure are unknown.
    - Law Alumni Association, 1963-1964 (2 folders) (Box 64)
    - Law Bulletin, 1964-1965 (Box 64)
    - Placement, Job and Area Preference, Class of 1963 (2nd year), undated (Box 64)
    - Memorandums, 1962-1967 (Box 64)
    - Lectureships, Associateships, fellowships, etcetera, 1962-1963 (Box 64)
    - Placement, Job and Area Preference, Class of 1962 (3rd year), undated (Box 64)
    - Recruiting, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Recruiting Trip, 1964-1965 (Box 64)
    - Rule of Law Center, 1964-1965, undated (Box 64)
    - S File, 1963-1965, undated (Box 64)
    - San Francisco, 1959-1963 (Box 64)
    - Scholarships, 1962-1964 (Box 64)
    - Securities Regulation Symposium, 1964-1968 (Box 64)
    - Small Buisness Studies, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Social Activities, Miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 64)
    - Speakers, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Student Loan Program, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Student Recommendations, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Students Seeking Jobs, 1963-1964 (Box 64)
    - Graduate Schools, 1959-1962 (Box 64)
    - Nathan Burkan Memorial Competition, 1956-1962 (Box 64)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1961-1963 (Box 64)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1959-1963 (Box 64)
    - Department of Labor, Washington D.C., 1962 (Box 64)
    - Department of the Interior, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960-1962 (Box 64)
    - Insurance Companies, 1961-1963 (Box 64)
    - Orientation Week, 1963, undated (Box 64)
    - Order of the Coif, 1964-1965 (Box 64)
    - Minutes, 1962-1967 (Box 65)
    - Banks, 1960-1964 (Box 65)
    - McGill University, Montreal, Canada, 1962 (Box 65)
    - Placement Questionaires, undated (Box 65)
    - Interviews, 1963-1965 (Box 65)
    - J File, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - Journal of Legal Education, 1963-1967, undated (Box 65)
    - Correspondence with Kentucky Regarding Changeover of the Journal of Legal Education, 1962-1966 (Box 65)
    - Judicial Board, 1963 (Box 65)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1963-1966 (Box 65)
    - L File, 1962-1967 (Box 65)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1967, undated (Box 65)
    - Moot Court, 1963-1967, undated (2 folders) (Box 65)
    - Institute of Government, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1962-1963 (Box 65)
    - Fellowships, 1961-1964 (Box 65)
    - United States Steel Corporation, 1961 (Box 65)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1962 (Box 65)
    - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, 1959-1963 (Box 65)
    - Law Clerks and Judges, 1961-1964 (Box 65)
    - Dow Chemical Corporation, 1960-1963 (Box 65)
    - Arthur Andersen and Company, 1964 (Box 65)
    - Corporations, 1960-1963 (Box 65)
    - Department of Agriculture, 1959-1962 (Box 65)
    - City of New York Civil Service Commission, 1963 (Box 65)
    - Bureau of the Budget, 1961-1963 (Box 65)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1962-1963 (Box 65)
    - Department of Justice, 1959-1965 (Box 65)
    - North Carolina Bar Association Institutes, 1963-1964 (Box 65)
    - North Carolina Bankers Association, 1963-1966 (Box 65)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1959-1963 (Box 65)
    - N file, 1962-1965 (Box 65)
    - Mordecai Society, 1963 (Box 65)
    - Medical Plan and Human Experimentation, 1964-1968 (Box 65)
    - Massachusetts Bar Review, 1963 (Box 65)
    - Loyalty Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 65)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1965, undated (Box 65)
    - Law Journal, 1962-1966, undated (Box 65)
    - Law School Alumni Association, 1966, undated (Box 65)
    - Law Dames, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - Rufus Powell, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Placement, Firms that have Visited our Campus, 1963-1965 (Box 65)
    - Placement Bulletin, 1968 (Box 65)
    - Phi Delta Phi, General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 65)
    - Peace Corps, 1963, undated (Box 65)
    - Personal and Placement, 1962-1964, undated (Box 65)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1963 (Box 65)
    - University Financial Aid Committee, 1963-1965, undated (Box 65)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1962-1963 (Box 65)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, undated (Box 65)
    - North Carolina National Bank, 1967-1968 (Box 65)
    - Federal Reserve System, 1959-1963 (Box 65)
    - Government, General, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1960-1962 (Box 65)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1960-1963 (Box 65)
    - Department of Navy, 1959-1961 (Box 65)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 65)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1960-1962 (Box 65)
    - Sunset Motor Company, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - Travel, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - Triangle Investment Club, 1953, 1964-1967, undated (Box 65)
    - Triangle Telecasters, 1967-1968, undated (Box 65)
    - Tsow, William, 1968 (Box 65)
    - University Admissions, 1962-1964 (Box 65)
    - University Calendar, 1964 (Box 65)
    - Wachovia Bank and Trust, 1964 (Box 65)
    - Athletic Association, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Duke University National Council, 1963-1965 (Box 65)
    - Durham Council on Human Relations, undated (Box 66)
    - E File, 1965, undated (Box 66)
    - Estate Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 66)
    - Faculty, 1965-1968, undated (Box 66)
    - Faculty Newsletter, 1965-1968 (Box 66)
    - Federal Taxation, 1964 (Box 66)
    - Foundation Press, 1963-1966 (Box 66)
    - Grades, 1964-1965, undated (Box 66)
    - Graduate Study Committee, 1963-1965, undated (Box 66)
    - Graduates, 1964 (Box 66)
    - H File, 1963-1966 (Box 66)
    - I File, 1963 (Box 66)
    - International Law Practice, 1962-1964 (Box 66)
    - International Law Society, 1963-1964 (Box 66)
    - Mens Graduate Center, 1964-1965 (Box 66)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1961-1962 (Box 66)
    - Income, 1963-1966 (Box 66)
    - North Carolina State Bar, 1966 (Box 66)
    - Public Service Faculty, 1961 (Box 66)
    - Placement, 1962-1967 (Box 66)
    - Research Council, 1965-1966 (Box 66)
    - Subdivision Control, 1967-1968 (Box 66)
    - Research and Writing, 1963-1967 (Box 66)
    - University Scholarship Committee, 1953, 1962-1963 (Box 66)
    - Annotated Reports System, 1961-1962 (Box 66)
    - West Publishing Company, 1962-1964 (Box 66)
    - Undergraduate Judicial Code, 1966 (Box 66)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 66)
  - Associate Dean Anthony Harrington, 1967-1971.
    Anthony Harrington was an associate dean of the law school; the exact dates of his tenure are unknown.
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 66)
- Law School Publications, 1934-1991, undated., 2.25 Linear Feet (1.5 boxes)
  This series contains records from both student and faculty law school publications. More information about publications can be found in the deans records.
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Annual Reports, 1954-1970 (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Minutes of the Editorial Advisory Committee, 1947-1957 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Publicity, 1949-1956 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Minutes of the Meetings of the Editorial Board and other Memoranda, 1934-1938 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Growth Policy (Possible Symposium Issue), 1975-1980 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Human Rights, 1979-1980 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Editorial Advisory Board, 1962-1968 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Accounting Symposium, 1965-1967, undated (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Air Pollution Source Materials, 1968 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Publicity, Air Pollution Control Symposium, 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Publicity, Medical Progress Issues, 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Publicity, the Middle East Crisis, 1969 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Publicity, Safety Symposium, 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Editorial Advisory committee, 1958-1959 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Annual Reports to Editorial Advisory Board, 1934, 1945-1957 (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Annual Report to the President, 1965-1970 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Dean's Report to the President, 1967 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Dean's Report to the President, 1964-1968 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Annual Report to the President of Duke University, 1949-1960 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Dean's Report to the President, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Expenses Book, 1933-1946 (Box 67)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, Review Notices Scrapbook, 1933-1938 (Box 67)
  - The Bar Rag, June 1946-March 1950 (Box 67)
  - The Bar Rag, September 1950-May 1954 (Box 67)
  - The Bar Rag, October 1954-March 1958 (Box 67)
  - The Bar Rag, October 1958-April 1960 (Box 67)
  - Duke Law Reporter, December 1960-May 1962 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 1-3, 1964-1965 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 4-7, 1966-1967 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 8-12, 1968-1970 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 13-15, 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 16-17, 1972 (Box 67)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Volumes 18-20, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - The Devil's Advocate, Various Issues, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Duke Environmental Law and Policy Forum Publication, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Duke Law Magazine, 1982-1987 (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - The Prolocuter, 1949-1951, 1962 (Box 68)
  - The Prolocuter, 1954, 1956-1958, 1960 (Box 68)